ISABEL HANKES

2123 Esquire Dr Anchorage, AK 99517

T 605.389.2630

isabel.hankes@gmail.com izthebest.github.io

Profile

Homeschooled Junior passionate about computer science. Girls Who Code alumni and knowledgable in various computer programming languages. Experience teaching and assisting students at charter school. Member of FPCS Student Government, representing the school in district meetings and statewide legislation, as well as promote respect, love, and professionalism.

Experience

Family Partnership Charter School | Volunteer Library Aide October 2016 - Present | Anchorage, AK

- Organize FPCS's collection of textbooks, curriculums, supplementary reading resources, fictional books, and media
- Assist students, parents, and teachers to easily find homeschool materials

Girls Who Code Summer Immersion Program | Student

July 2016 - August 2016 | Seattle, WA

- Experimented with Scratch, Python, Arduino Robots, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, APIs, mongoDB, nodeJS, and jade
- Strengthened leadership and teamwork skills while working on a final project;
 created a social connectivity platform to support and connect teenagers struggling with mental illnesses such as depression or anxiety

Military Youth Leadership Summit | Participant June 2016 | Eglin AFB, FL

• Developed leadership skills while competing in team building exercises

Hickam Air Force Base Commissary | Bagger October 2015 - April 2016 | Honolulu, HI

• Provided quality bagging service to veterans and active duty military members

Education

Family Partnership Charter School September 2016 - Present I Anchorage AK